<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_label1">Privacy Agreement</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_content1">We take your privacy very seriously and this Privacy Agreement explains how we collect, use and protect your personal information. </string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_label2">Information collected</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_content2">This app requires permission to read files and listen to notifications so that you can use its functions. If these permissions are not granted, the use of some functions may be affected. Other than that, we will not collect, store or share any personal information about you. \nWe do not collect sensitive information such as your device identifiers, location information, calendar, contacts, text messages, call logs, camera or microphone. </string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_label3">Information usage</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_content3">This application is not connected to the Internet, so none of your information will be transmitted anywhere. We will only use the permissions you have granted to provide corresponding functions when you use this application. \nWe will not collect, store, share or use any personal information from your device. We also do not use any technology to personally identify you or track your online activities. </string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_label4">Information Protection</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_content4">This application of ours is open source, so you can always view its source code to ensure that we do not obtain your personal information. We will take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We will comply with applicable privacy laws and regulations and will update this Privacy Agreement from time to time. \nIf you have any questions or suggestions about this privacy agreement, please feel free to contact us. </string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_label5">Authorization</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_content5">This project may contain some commercial resources, but this application is not for commercial profit purposes, so if you find that this application contains unauthorized resources from you or others, please contact us in time . \nIf you do not want us to use these resources, we will delete them as soon as possible. </string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_label6">Other</string>
    <string name="privacy_agreement_content6">This app of ours may contain third-party links to other websites or services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third-party sites or services. We strongly recommend that you carefully read the privacy policies of these third-party websites or services before visiting them. \nWe reserve the right to make changes or updates to this Privacy Policy in the future. If we make changes or updates to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated version on this page and provide a notice within the app. If you continue to use our app, you agree to the updated privacy policy. </string>
</resources>